[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Harrison Ford stars in Blade Runner.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie, released in 1976, is Alfred Hitchcocks final completed movie?", "correct_answer": "Family Plot", "incorrect_answers": ["Topaz", "Frenzy", "Torn Curtain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fox hunting was made illegal in the U.K. in 2005.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the advertising slogan of a peanut butter brand: \u201cChoosy mothers choose ______", "correct_answer": "Jif", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Pan", "Planters", "Skippy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character said, She lied, she lied to us.?", "correct_answer": "General Moff Tarkin", "incorrect_answers": ["Darth Vader", "Emperor Palpatine", "Han Solo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the popular TV show, at what restaurant does Alice work?", "correct_answer": "Mels Diner", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennys", "Burger King", "McDonalds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is considered the first American to be killed in the Cold War?", "correct_answer": "John Birch", "incorrect_answers": ["Alan Funt", "Allen Dulles", "William Donovan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This herb, regarded as the king of herbs in many cooking books, is also known as Albahaca and St. Josephs Wort.", "correct_answer": "Basil", "incorrect_answers": ["Bergamot", "Annato", "Calamus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As far as disguising is concerned, octopuses are among the most proficient species in nature.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chromatin, found in the nucleus of a cell, consists of a complex of Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), the gene-carrying molecule. Which of the following types of chromatin is rich in genes?", "correct_answer": "euchromatin", "incorrect_answers": ["heterochromatin", "facultative heterochromatin", "constitutive heterochromatin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chess a backwards move is almost always a bad move.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The United States had 50 deaths from the Ebola Virus in the period from 1976 to 2006.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]